123calendars.com 2005-05-21

# 123 Posters Privacy Policy

> You are here: Home Help 123Posters Privacy Policy
> 
> **PRIVACY POLICY**
> 
> 
> Your privacy is guaranteed at 123Posters.com. We have provided this page explaining our information management procedures so that you know you can enjoy our website without worrying about your privacy.
> 
> We understand that privacy is important, so we do not collect any information about visitors to our site unless asked to do so, (for example, by filling out a form or sending an e-mail.) Like you, we hate ‘SPAM’ (unsolicited e-mails) and encourage you to take action against people who send it. Any information used to place orders or complete forms on this site is considered to be confidential and private. We never sell, give or trade our mailing list or other information about our customers. We do not store credit card information on the site. You will only receive e-mail from us (other than in the normal course of processing your order) if you specifically request to be on one of the mailing lists.
> 
> **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**
> 
> **Orders:** To process your credit card orders, we must know your name, mailing address, e-mail address, credit card number and expiration date. This information lets us process your order and ship it to you as well as notify you of your order status. We also must know your name and mailing address to process mail orders with a check or money order. The information collected to process your order is only used for that purpose and is held in the strictest confidence. Note: You must be 13 years of age or older to place an order online.
> 
> **Quiz:** If you participate in our 123 Posters Music Trivia Quiz, we ask for your first name and e-mail address to notify the winner of the quiz. The quiz winner will be notified by e-mail and will need to supply his or her name and mailing address to receive the prize. The information collected for the quiz is only used for that purpose. Note: You must be 13 years of age or older to participate.
> 
> **Mailing List Sign Up:** If you wish to sign up for the 123 Posters Mailing List, you must provide your name and e-mail address. This information is used to inform you about new products, services, special offers, information, or functionality changes about 123 Posters. This information is not gathered for this purpose when you place an order. You must separately sign up to be on the 123 Posters Mailing list. You must confirm that you are 13 years of age or older to sign up for the mailing list. Note: You must be 13 years of age or older to sign up.
> 
> **Auction Registration:** If you wish to bid at the 123Posters Auction, you must first register to create a User ID and password. This registration information is used only for the 123Posters Auction and is never reused for any other purpose. The information is held in the strictest confidence. Note: You must be 18 years of age or older to participate.
> 
> **HOW WE USE THIS INFORMATION**
> 
> **Orders:** 123 Posters only collects and uses your personal information from orders (name, e-mail address, mailing address, and credit card or banking information) to process and fulfill orders and to provide notification of order status. 
> 
> **Quiz:** Information collected from the Quiz (name and e-mail address -- and name and address of quiz winner) is only used for the purpose of sending the winner the prize. 
> 
> **Mailing List Sign Up:** Information collected for our mailing list sign-up is used to inform you about new products, services, special offers, information, or functionality changes at 123 Posters. You can remove your name from the list at any time.
> 
> **Auction Registration:** Registration information for the 123Posters Auction is used only to validate bids placed on auction items (for example, to check that the User ID and password match). 
> 
> **YOUR CONSENT**
> 
> By using our website, you agree that we may use your information as stated above. If we change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page.
> 
> **CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**
> 
> You must be over 13 years of age to place an order, enter a quiz, sign up for our mailing list, or participate in any online activity at 123 Posters where you enter personal information. 
> 
> In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children 13 years or age or younger. 
> 
> **HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION**
> 
> When you place an order, that information moves to a secure server. The "Secure Server Software" (SSL) encrypts all information you input before sending it, protecting your information from unauthorized access. 
> 
> Please contact us at info@123posters.com or call us at (530) 474-4192 (Monday to Friday from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. Pacific Time) with any questions that you might have regarding this privacy policy.
